Robin Hoover Papers, 1981-2010
University of Arizona Libraries,Special Collections
Robin Hoover Papers 1981-2010
MS 468
Hoover, Robin
This collection primarily concerns itself with the issue of migrant workers and their plight as they cross the US-Mexico border. Most of the material is in VHS or DVD format comprised of segments of news programming from various broadcast television and cable programs.
11 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Notes on Use of Collection
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Further accruals are expected.
Biographical Note
The Reverend Robin (Robert Lane) Hoover, Ph.D. is a native of Big Spring, Texas. It was in Texas that Hoover attended Texas Christian University where he earned a Bachelor’s in Journalism and Religion. He went on to earn a Masters of Divinity Degree with an emphasis in social ethics from Brite Divinity School of Texas Christian University. Texas Tech University awarded Robin Hoover a Ph.D. in Political Science in 1998. Since 1980, Hoover has served continuously as a full time pastor in Disciples Congregations. Active in providing services to migrant people, Hoover has distinguished himself as a leader and a visionary. It was in Tucson, Arizona that Hoover founded and served as the inaugural president of Humane Borders, Inc., a social welfare corporation providing humanitarian assistance to migrants risking their lives crossing the Mexico-US border in Arizona. Hoover advocates major changes in US immigration/migration policies.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into five series
Series I: Publications, 1998-Ongoing
Series II: Research Files, 1994-Ongoing
Series III: Personal Materials, 1981-Ongoing
Series IV: Awards and Artifacts, 1998-Ongoing
Series V: Audiovisual Material 1996-Ongoing
Scope and Content Note
The bulk of this collection is from 2000-2005 and focuses on the organization, Humane Borders, Inc., that Robin Hoover founded. The collection is mainly VHS and DVD copies of broadcasts from local and national news programs discussing migrant workers, immigration reform and the Humane Borders organization. These segments and programs concern themselves exclusively with issues related to immigration. Also included are a scattering of newspaper articles on the same subjects. A collection of plaques, awards and personal calendars is also included. The collection includes Robin Hoover’s dissertation from Texas Tech University as well as drafts and materials compiled while writing the dissertation, including notes and audio tapes of interviews with subjects relating to the topic of the dissertation. This collection is mainly concerned with the issue of immigration from Mexico to the United States along the Southern Arizona border.
Access Terms
Hoover, Robin
Humane Borders, Inc.
Illegal Aliens
Human Smuggling
United States Emigration and immigration
Mexico Emigration and immigration
Mexican-American Border Region
Arizona
Tucson (Ariz.)
Photographs
Pamphlets
Plaques
Container List
- Series I: Publications, 1998-2004
  This series consists of material published by Robin Hoover. It is arranged alphabetically, then chronologically. It contains audio cassettes, computer disks, drafts of works, newspaper articles and a copy of Hoover’s dissertation.
  - Dissertation, August 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dissertation- 3.5" Disks, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dissertation- Audio Recordings, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dissertation- Audio Recording Notes #1, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dissertation- Audio Recording Notes #2, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dissertation- Draft, June 16, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dissertation- Field Work #1, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dissertation- Field Work #2, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Series II: Research Files, 1994-2010
  This series contains newspaper articles and other publications; such as workbooks, phone directories and reports.
  - Immigration Deathly Adventure, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Migrant, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2004-2010 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Report from the Border, February 13, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Refugee and Immigrant Resource Directory, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Series III: Personal Materials, 1981-2009
  This series consists of a few photographs pertaining to the Humane Borders organization and pocket calendars spanning three decades. One oversize image is located in Box 6.
  - Photographs, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Pocket Calendars, 1981-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pocket Calendars, 1997-2009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Awards and Artifacts, 1998-2010
  This series contains mostly awards and plaques. Also included are examples of the water station flags from a water stations that Humane Borders maintains. Box 5 in this series contains oversize material.
  - Cesar Chavez Humanitarian Award, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Eugene Mackaben Community Service Award, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fundacion Mexico, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Founder’s Day Parade, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Humane Borders, 20053 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Leo B. Hart Humanitarian Award, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous awards, 1998-2010 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rosa Parks Living History Makers, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - University of Arizona Alumni Association, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Water Station Flags, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Community Service Award, September 19, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - El Gobierno del Estado de Sonora, January 15, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - El Gobierno del Estado de Sonora, August 31, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Framed Caricature, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lulac, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Oversize Picture, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series V: Audiovisual Material, 1996-2008
  This series is comprised heavily of VHS and DVD copies of news broadcasts. The majority of VHS tapes have DVD copies. And while not every DVD has a VHS copy, many do. There is also one CD and one audiocassette tape, which have been marked.
  - Chicano – “Taking Back the Schools,” 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fighting for Political Power, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rights to Food Campaign in India, July 1, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Church and Activist Groups Help Migrant Workers 1, 2: The O’Reilly Factor, September 10, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Border Watch I., II., September 10, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Border Watch III., September 11, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Well-Founded Fear, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Michael Morton (compact disc)– Sanctuary, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dangerous Crossing I, January 4, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Humanitarian Assistance: The O’Reilly Factor, January 10, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 130 Migrants Apprehended, Plan for Water Stations, February 1, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Border Patrol Public Service Announcements, February 1, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Border Patrol Public Service Announcement (Original), February 1, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Migrants Apprehended, Hoover Comments, February 1, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - First Deployment Clips, March 19, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Desert Water Stations Story, March 28, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Migrant Encounter, April 18, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Death of 14, Marcos in Wellton, AZ, May 23, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Death of 14, Robin Hoover Comments, May 23, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Funeral Procession for 12 Bodies, May 13, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bodies shipped to Vera Cruz, May 31, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Funeral Procession, May 31, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Robin Hoover at Studio, June 1, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hot Water, June 1, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Border Patrol Strategy-Death in the Desert, June 1, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Nueva Frontera-Gate Keeper, June 3, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Senator Kolbe: Resources on the Border, June 6, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Pima County $25,000 to Humane Borders, June 6, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Robin Hoover at Supervisor’s Meeting, June 6, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Humane Borders on the News, June 13, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Humane Borders Water Stations, June 31, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Humane Borders in the News, May and June 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sierrita Mountain Water Station, June 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Border Patrol releases, June 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The New Frontier: High School Students Crossing the Border, June 2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dangerous Crossing, July 4, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Interview with Fidel Alonzo-Mireles, July 14, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Nogales Meals Incident Mateo Perez Gomez, July 16, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Border Patrol 4 Public Announcements, August 29, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Border Patrol: Deaths in the Desert, August 29, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Along the Line, September 21, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Death Numbers, September 21, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Beyond the Border, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Beyond the Border: Mas Alla de la Frontera, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - News 13 Simulations to Cross the Desert, Fall 2001-Spring 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - News Clips, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Water Stations Anniversary, February 24, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Water Stations I., February 27, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Border Patrol, March 1, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Border Patrol Video Announcement, March 1, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Migrant Exhibition, March 4, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Robin Hoover at BA Water Stations, March 7, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Water Station Vandalism I., March 9, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Hannity and Colmes, May 13, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - $40 Million Claim, May 13, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - $40 Million Lawsuit, May 15, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dangerous Crossings II., May 19, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Destroying the Desert, May 20, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Politically Incorrect, May 21, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - First Anniversary of 14 Migrant Deaths, May 23, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Death on a Friendly Border Original, June 1, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mexican Public Service Announcements, June 1, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Water on Reservation, June 9, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Samaritan Patrol I., July 1, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Samaritan Patrol III., July 1, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Samaritan Patrol II., July 7, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Senator Edward Kennedy and Senator Arlen Specter, July 7, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - American Border Patrol, July 24, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Interview with Bill Walker, August 1, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Deal with the Devil, August 8, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - ACLU Hearing, August 23, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New Water Stations, August 23, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Humanitarian Assistance, August 28, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - March for Migrants Memorial, September 29, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Interviews with Enrique Marones, October 1, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Donahue Show, November 12, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Tombstone Militia, December 3, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Robin Hoover in Studio- O’odham Comments, December 6, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Report from the Border 2003, Part I., February 13, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Report from the Border 2003, Part II., February 13, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - A Walk through Cabeza Prieta, February 13, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Lawsuit: 14 Migrant Deaths, May 6, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - $14 Million Lawsuit, May 7, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Lawsuit: Heartland, May 16, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Border Chaos, May 16, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Water Station Dedication, July 20, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Paul Fuschini I., August 9, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Paul Fushini and David Ray, August 9, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Christ Dies and Lives on the Border, August 2003 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Del Rio Deportation, September 10, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Anti-Immigrant Vigilantism, October 7, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Gotas de Vida, October 2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - The Revolution will not be Televised, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bill O’Reilly, February 1, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - World News Tonight, May 18, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Illegal Crossing, May 18, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Water Stations II., June 1, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hot Water, June 9, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Death in the Desert: Frontline, June 2004 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - The Big Story, July 13, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Terrorist Alley, August 16, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Board of Supervisors Meeting, September 1, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pima County Contract, September 8, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - March for Migrants, September 26, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Memorial and March for Migrants, September 26, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - From Altar to Phoenix, December 17, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - American Immigration, December 17, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Endless Exodus, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Farmingville, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - The Fourth World War, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - The Gatekeeper, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Play Media To[u]r for Humane Borders, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Shadow of Hope, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - This is What Free Trade Looks Like, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Water Station Map, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New Border Technologies, March 6, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Dying to Live, March 25, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Coyote Crossing, March 2005 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Arizona Illustrated, April 4, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Adventures with El Gordo, April 22, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Water Station Map, May 8, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Paul Fuschini Speaks on Warning Map, May 11, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Warning Map, May 12, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Warning Map: Hannity and Colmes, May 12, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Warning Poster, May 20, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Warning Posters, May 20, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Salt Lake City and Santa Cruz Volunteers, May 21, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - O’Reilly Factor, May 26, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Reporter’s Roundtable, June 3, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 5th Anniversary of Humane Borders, June 11, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Last Stop, June 13, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Robin Hoover: Nightly News, June 13, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Methodist March for Migrants, July 14, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - World Harmony, Can it Happen?, July 15, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - A Walk in the Desert, July 2005 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Illegal Immigrant Memorial, September 25, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Trip to Altar and Sasabe, October 23, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Dying to Get In, December 11, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Border Stories, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Bridge / Puente, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - de Nadie, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - State of County Presentation, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Walking the Line, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Women Crossing Borders, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Governor’s State of the State: AZ Illustrated, January 10, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 6th Annual March for Migrants, January 10, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Robin Hoover Announcing Mexican Trip, January 19, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Sue Goodman with Warning Poster, January 19, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Mexico Trip Robin Hoover Warning Poster, January 19, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Lou Dobbs reports on Warning Posters, Rubin in Mexico City, January 24 2006 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Paul Fuschini II., January 24, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Paul Fuschini Warning Posters I, January 24, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Humane Borders Warning Posters, January 26, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Robin Hoover Map Project, January 26-27, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Religion and Ethics, February 26, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Robin Hoover Comment on Four Migrant Deaths, March 12, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Reaction to President, March 16, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Al Franken in Fresno, March 30, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Border Walls, March 31, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Randall Pinkston Altar, Mexico, April 22, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Randall Pinkston Identifying Deceased, April 23, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Deadly Desert, May 7, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Response to President, May 15, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Response to Bush’s visit to Yuma, May 18, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Daybreak, June 14, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Minuteman, Fence, Vandalism, June 16, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Immigration Debate, June 16, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Minuteman with Immigrant Family: 30 Days, July 1, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Migrant Trash, July 30, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Narco Commido, August 1, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Naomi’s New Morning, August 1, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - The Poverty Trap with Bill Clinton, September 2, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Water Stations III, September 21, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Migrant Memorial, October 1, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Humane Borders Power Point, October 10, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Premio National de Derechos Humanos, December 13, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Robin Hoover at Los Pinos, December 13, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - In the Shadow of the American Dream, December 26, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Crossing Arizona, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - The Invisible Mexicans of Deer Canyon, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - The Power of Community, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Sustainable Table, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - I.G.E. Meeting SBI Cell Phones, January 24, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Service in IFNM, February 18, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Conferencia, February 23, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Power Point, March 27, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Humane Borders on the News, April 8, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - New Sanctuary Movement, May 9, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Sanctuary, May 10, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Migrant Deaths, May 14, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Trash Cleanup, May 23, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Guatemalan Girls Split from Family, August 2, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Conteo Noche, June 16, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Board of Supervisors Meeting, August 5, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Board Meetings, Agenda, September 11, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Aventura en el Desierto, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Beyond Borders, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - A Future with Hope, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - The Invisible Chapel, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Migrant’s Journey, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - American Dream Dead or Alive, March 13, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Tires Slashed Security Camera Video, August 9, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - David Garcia and Mike Wilson at Press Conference, September 4, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Mike Wilson at Press Conference in 30 Minutes, September 7, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Arizona, December 17-18, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - The Devil’s Highway, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - One Border One Body, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - A Sign of the Cross, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Wild Versus Wall, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Border Safety Initiative, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chipas El Gran Muro Para Los Migrantes, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - “The Chronicles of Life Outside the Law” (4 episodes), undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Crossing Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Crossing Arizona Unfinished Copy, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - El Drama de los Migrantes ante le Nueva Legislacion en Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Gotas da Vita, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Humane Borders Hearst Award Entries, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Humane Borders Power Point, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Multiple News Clips, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Paul Fuschini Warnig Poster I, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Samaritan Promo Tapes, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Surveillance and Rescue of Migrants in the Desert, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - TG3 Flavio Fusi Laredo Texas, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Water Station Map I, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Water Station Vandalism II, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Border Safety Initiative Public Service Announcement (audiocassette tape), undated (Box 20, Folder 20)